Chasing Taste is a comedy film directed by Sean Gannet.
A romantic comedy about food, love, and lies under an NYC Skyline.
Chase Guidry, played by Kirk McGee.
Katie Ryan, played by Uma Incrocci.
Palmer Guidry, played by Maitely Weismann.
A.J., played by Ryan McDonough.
Madison Hunt, played by Ashley Wren Collins.
Turtle Bay Tavern Patron, played by Cynthia Basinet.
Bad Taste is a 1987 New Zealand science-fiction action comedy horror film
written, produced, filmed, directed by and co-starring Peter Jackson.
Independently produced on a low budget, it is Jackson's first feature film.
Jackson and friends take on most of the key roles, both on and off-screen.
The plotline sees aliens invade the fictional New Zealand village of Kaihoro to harvest humans for their
intergalactic fast food franchise, where they face off against a four-man paramilitary force.
The film was shot in Northern Wellington over the course of four years, and eventually received nearly a quarter of a million dollars in
New Zealand Film Commission assistance, providing Jackson with the leverage necessary to advance in the film industry.
Since its release, Bad Taste has become a cult film
and has received stronger reviews.
In 2008, British film magazine Empire ranked Bad Taste
as the 416th greatest film ever made.
The tone is lighthearted.